Hello and welcome to this video in this YouTube video you're going to learn about great parallel development.
So first we need to learn about the branching operation.
So we use branches as pointers to our comets or snapshots.
Remember what I told you about comets when we create a comet we are actually creating a snapshot of
our project and that snapshot is going to contain all of the updated codes.
Our project but it is actually the updated project.
So that is going to be our comet or in other words our snapshots of our project.
So we have our main branch that is also called the master branch.
So remember when we were actually entering our bash coats in our terminal Terminal application or inside
the bash application we entered the origin master.
There we were actually referring to the master branch.
So the master branch is actually your main project your main code.
First we have the main branch or the main project.
Next we have something called working on a new feature.
So for example you are working on a chat application and you want to add up for example voice chat feature
to your app.
So in that case this means that you want to add a new feature to your application.
And in this case we recommend that you do not mess up with the main branch that is going to be your
main project because you want to add a new feature and this feature can cause a little bit of problems.
Or maybe it can cause a buck inside the main project.
So first you want to make sure that this feature works perfectly and then you want to add this project.
Is this a new feature to your main branch.
So in this case we are going to create a new branch in order to work on the project that is called parallel
development.
So we have two branches which is fine.
The first one is the main branch.
The second branch is also our main project our project but we want to add a new feature to the project.
So in this case we are going to use the parallel development in order to work on the new branch and
the new feature.
And then when it works fine and we know that it works perfectly we are going to add this feature to
the main branch.
So in this case we do not mess up with the main branch or the autogen mass there.
So we create our new plant from a comet or snapshot.
So remember what they told you about comets.
Right.
We create a climate and or a snapshot.
So if we create a new branch there in order to add the new feature.
So now let's be clear about the kinds of branches.
We have two kinds of branches.
The first one is the local branches views local branches inside our local system or workspace that can
be used in our local repository.
In other words the local branches are actually local to our computer or the local repository that we
are working with the same kind.
Is there a remote tracking branches.
So it is just a connection between the local repository and the central repository the remote tracking
branches.
It's just going to connect to that local repository to the central repository.
So now let's go ahead and learn about branches practically.
So here on Windows we have these kids Passhe application.
If you are using Macs you need to use the terminal application after installing the kids.
So now if you just go ahead and open the file they're going to right click here and then click on get
past here.
So if you're using Mac you just need to manually just change the direction to this folder to the folder
that is named as Android desiccate.
So the first thing that you can see here is this mass there inside the prentices dismasted keyboard.
This means that we are currently working on the master of branch.
So in this way we can understand that currently we are working on which branch.
So for now it is master.
So in order to create our new branch we just simply needs to type in here get branch
make sure that you don't have to type it here and then space.
So next we just need to put the name of the branch you can name it whatever you want but make sure that
this is a meaningful name.
So this is going to be our first branch.
I'm going to just put to put here if we.
So this F. B stands for first branch and I'm going to press an entity on my keyboard.
So let's see what happens.
So now the first branch is created.
So now let me tell you something about this new branch that we created here.
This new branch is actually from the master branch or in other words.
This first branch that we created here is originated from the master branch.
This means that it contains all the codes of the master branch.
In other words it is just a clone of our main project but there is something different here.
You can see that we are still inside the master branch so it can be a little bit confusing but that's
OK.
This means that we need to switch to the new branch that we created here.
So in order to see to the new branch we just need to have been here get check out space and then the
name of the branch.
So if we make sure that is the name that you are referring to is exactly the same name that you created
that you set for the new branch.
So so mine is F.P. and I'm going to press the Enter key on my keyboard in order to see what happens.
So now it says switched to branch if B.
And here you can see inside the prentices.
It says if B.
So hopefully that makes sense.
So now let's go ahead and create a new job a file inside our Android dash gets folder.
So I'm going to type in here touch so because I'm using the Unix command.
That's why this command works here in windows inside the special application.
So touch and then space and then the name of the file.
So I'm going to name it as more of my Java and then pass on and take you on your keyboard.
So if you go ahead and open the Android that's good for there we should see this file here.
So here it is our job are fine and I'm going to open this file more by that Java so inside this file
Let's click Create on your class so you'll know that the name of your class must be the name the same
as the name of your file.
So this is going to be the more wide class.
So class more by opening calibrates followed by a closing brace.
So let me go ahead and increase the font size.
So just click on file and if you're using Mac you just need to click on intelligent idea at the top
and then go ahead and click on preferences or settings.
And then here editor forint.
So now you can increase the font size here and now inside this class we can also create a new method.
So I can't say Puplick so I'm going to type in here in main Mfat that that class this mobile class is
going to have so public static Voyt me and then he said the practice's stream.
Aure the data type of the prime with her and its name is going to be Ogg's.
So I just miss it.
I'm going to say I can hear system thoughts it's the print princeling
on inside the coats I'm going to type in hello for semicolon.
So I'm going to save this project this fight and I'm going to close it OK.
Now let's go back to our bash or the Terminal application.
So now I want to come to my changes my more avoid that job.
So first we need to add these more by double 5 to the get index and then we can commit our changes remember.
So first we need to say get it and then we need to refer to the name of our fine.
So Mauboy thought Java and then press on on your keyboard.
So if you type in here get status it should say that we need to commit Disneyfied.
So I'm going to say gets commits space dash em and then space inside the double quotes we need to typing
in a message.
So that message is going to be a more vile or I can't say Java.
As you can see I actually accidentally pressed on until on my keyboard and it is now it has come it
had this new change.
But here I just wanted to let you know that this new change is in the first branch.
It is not added to the master branch yet.
OK so say that because I just wanted to with a paint job class Moabite in the first branch.
So now you get the idea.
So here you can see that it says that it it does change it's actually committed and it says one file
changed here and here you can see the name of the file.
Moabite that Jarboe.
So here let me tell you that this the change that we added here is in the first branch or if B.
Right and in them origin master or in the main branch we don't have this change.
So if you type in here l s.
Notice that inside Apprentice's it says if B if you press an integer on your keyboard it's going to
list all of the files that we have in the main branch.
We have to lie in that job on mobile that job and all the other files.
So now let's go ahead and switch to the main branch to the origin master.
So let's just clear this area first because we have lots of code here.
I notice that here it says we're in that desktop Android good for there in the first branch.
So now let's go ahead and see what is happening.
What is inside that Master branch.
So I'm going to type in here.
Get check out space and then Sui's to that muscle branch so its name is M..
Right.
So now press on until key on your keyboard.
Now we are switched through the branch mass there.
And inside the this is you can see this Master.
Let's go ahead and take an L S.
Now we have like Java music that Java and all the other files but we don't have the Mauboy that java
file in the master Brandt's.
So now it's Challenge time.
Your challenge is to go ahead and create a new directory on your desktop and name it as chat app and
then create a new file and the name is named as voice chat.
But this voice chat file should be in the new branch.
You can name it whatever you want but it should be added in the new branch and then you can add changes
there and then make sure to list the files that you have inside the folder that you are actually adding
that new branch.
That is for the voice chat in the new branch and you are not messing up with the master branch and make
sure that inside your master branch you have some other files so that you can see the difference.
So give this challenge a go and good luck.
So now it's time to learn about merging.
So now assume that we have the master branch right so the master branch all told you is the production
ready project.
This is the project that is going to have the updated codes.
It is going to be the project that we are going to for example if it is an Android app.
This is going to be the project that we want to upload to the Google Play store.
So this is the project that we want.
We don't want to mess up.
So now for example its name IIS chat app.
Ok now we want to add a new feature called voice chat to the application but we don't want to just interrupt
the master branch.
So now we are creating a new branch and its name is FP.
So for example if B stands for first branch the name of the feature is voice chat feature and for example
it is done.
We have successfully added the voice voice chat feature to our application.
So now what.
Now it's time to merge back in this feature to our final project to our production ready project by
using the merging operation.
OK now that we have the new feature it's time to merge it back to the master branch.
So let's go ahead and let's see how it's done.
So now open your bash application or your terminal application.
If you're using Mac and here make sure that you are in the master branch first.
If you are not.
Make sure to check out the master branch because the master branch is the target.
You want to merge back.
Our first branch to our Master branch.
So make sure that instead Apprentice's it is mass there and here the command that we are going to use
is get marriage and then the name of the branch so the name of our branch is.
If the so before I before I press Enter key on my keyboard just take a look at these lists.
Here we have the line and all of these files.
But we don't have more why the java file inside the master branch.
I'm going to execute this command by pressing on my key on my keyboard.
Now I'm going to type in here l s in order to see what I have inside there.
M. branch so not.
Is this more by the java file is added to the master branch.
OK so let me clear this area for you.
So another important point that I want you to know about is that the first branch still exists.
OK we just merged our first branch to our Master branch but the first branch still exists and you can
check out to the first branch and if you want to you can add new features to your application to your
project and then just made it back into the master branch.
So for example I can't say get check out if B.
So not inside the prentices you can see that via checked out or you are switched to their branch.
And then we can go ahead and open the Android Dashti there and then go ahead and open them more while
the Java fight next.
Let's go ahead and modify this file.
So I'm going to add one more line of code here.
One more statement and this time I'm going to say Hollywood word.
So now let's go ahead and save this project and close it and then we can go ahead to our Basche application
or the terminal application and then inside the first branch I'm going to come it's my changes.
But here let me tell you that because we just modified our already existing Java find inside this android
that dasht get full there.
We don't have to necessarily at our file today get index because it is all of the data we just modified
it.
So in order to commit our change we can just say kids commit dash
dash em.
So I know that we use this command in order to add multiple files to the index.
But here because we have already this file inside a folder and we just modify it then I'm going to use
this dash 8 here in order to also add these change to the index to the get indexed so we don't have
to type in here to get ADD and then the name of the file.
But using this dash 8.
We are already also adding this change to the get index and also commenting it gets by using dash M
and then inside the double quotes.
I can say modified the more about the Java fight inside the first branch and then person until January
but in order to execute this command.
Now if I type in here get status.
Now here you can see that it says that on branch if b nothing to come in.
So it is already committed here you can see it says modified at the moment that justified inside the
first branch.
So this is actually the message so I have a typo here also.
And here you can see that it has modified the movement wide that Java find inside the first branch.
So hopefully that makes sense.
And now we can go ahead and Mitsch back our first branch to our origin master to our origin branch or
the master branch how first you need to check out to our Master branch the master branch is that destination.
So I'm going to say get check out.
And then the name of the branch which is the master now in say the Prentice's it says master.
Now I'm going to go ahead and type in here get marriage.
I'm going to merge back our first branch to L.M. branch so it gets merge if the done.
Now here it says updating.
Now our changes are done and it's just one file changed.
So I just cleared this area for you so you can see what's going on here Beder.
Here you can see that we are still inside the master branch but how do you know that something is changed.
How do I know what is modified actually.
So we have a comment for that.
You just need to type in here.
Cat space.
And in the name of the file.
So of what it is more by DOT Java Java.
Find some that Java.
So here let me tell you that you must be inside this directory and really Dasch get.
And in the massive branch so that you can see that what is changed inside the master branch and then
press enter on your keyboard.
So here we have the class mobile and inside this class we have the Smurfette and we have these two lines
of code.
But the second line of code system that ousted princeling.
It is added in the last update so you can see that it every team is committed perfectly and you can
also use this command in another branch.
For example in your first branch or a B you can use this command in order to see what is actually modified
and then decide whether you want to marriage back that change that branch to your master or branch or
not.
So you can't.
You just need to use chat and then the name of the file that you have changed or modified so now that
you have learned about the merging operation it's Challenge time.
Go ahead and add that voice chat feature that you have created in the last challenge.
Go ahead and merge that into your master branch.
So good luck.
So now that we have learnt about the merging operation it's time to learn about the rebase operation.
So the rebase operation does actually the same job the same task as the merging does.
OK but in a different way in a linear manner.
So based on my own experience it's better to learn about the rebasing operation practically.
So let's go ahead and open our bash for Terminal application.
Let's see what is actually rebasing.
So first let's clear this area and then let's Sui's to the first branch.
So I'm going to type in here.
Get check out it the.
Now let's go ahead and open our Android that is fine and I'm going to go ahead.
And here we can either create the next device.
But if you want to create jobs files you can do it here in your bash or terminal application.
So I'm going to type in here touch and then the name of the file.
So the first one is going to be a boxer Dart's Java file and another file Let's go ahead and say touch
each boxer dot Java.
OK.
Now if you go ahead and open your folder you should see these two files the set and the kickboxer.
And then let's go ahead and open the box file.
So here we don't have to create a class.
I just want to modify this fine sand going out and tell a value.
I can say DCs Boxer and then save is fine clothes it's next go ahead and open the kickboxer file.
And here let's also modify this file.
So this is kickboxer save it and then close it OK.
Now let's go back to our Flash application.
So here make sure that you are already inside the first branch and then to create these two files the
boxes and the kickboxer.
So now that we created these two files we need to add these two files to get indexed so we have multiple
files here right.
So you need to say get space dash get space at dash and then a capitol a.
This is very important.
Get app space dash Capitol a because we have multiple files you want to add multiple files to the index.
So I'm going to present to the German Keeble get status.
So here it says that we have these two files and we need to commit them.
So I'm going to say get space come eat space dash 8.
We have multiple flights right.
We want to commit all of these flights.
So that's why I said that lowercase leader a space dash him space and an inside double quotes the message.
So I'm going to say Boxer and teach Boxer Dobber files.
It's next let's go ahead and execute this command by pressing the Enter key on our keyboard.
So here you can see that it has two files changed.
We are inside the first branch so I can say good status in order to see that it says nothing to it.
So everything works fine.
So let's clear this area.
So now if you go ahead and type in here it's inside the first branch we have two new Newfies boxes that
Java and kickboxer Java.
But if you go ahead and type in here get check out to the master branch and type in here.
And as you can see that we don't have their boxer and kickboxer double points here.
So let's go back let's go ahead and switch to the first branch.
So good checkout if we are going to say that we are inside the first branch and I'm going to type in
here.
Get space replace M..
So notice that you are inside the first branch and we are using this command to get rebase master so.
So now let's go ahead and press on until you are on a keyboard and let's see what happens.
So now it says the current branch if B is up to date.
So this means that now that we've replaced our first branch to our Master branch now it is up to date
that everything that we have inside the master master branch is actually inside the first branch.
That's why it says it is up to date.
So now let's go ahead and let's switch to the master branch.
So now I am inside the master branch.
I just clear this area for you.
So in order to suit to the master branch you know what to do get checked out and then the name of the
branch.
Now I am going to do the same command in reverse order.
I'm going to say get notice that I am inside the master of range gets rebase and then this time I'm
going to be fair to my first branch or F. B and then press on into the key on your keyboard.
So now let's see what what's happening it says first rebinding head to replay your work on top of it.
Fast forward that master to the.
So this means that it is actually adding all of the commits of the first branch to the head of the master
branch.
So this is the same as the merging operation but it is doing it in a linear order.
So in this way the advantage of using rebase operation is that we have less branches and everything
is done linearly.
And I think rebase is better but you can use whatever you want.
You can either use marriage or rebase.
So now that we are inside the master branch if I type in here and S and press on energy on my keyboard
you can see that you have the boxer and the kickboxer that job afarid inside the master right.
So it's works perfectly.
So now it's challenge time.
Go ahead and create a new feature.
This means I mean you need to create on your file and you want to add the emoji feature to your chat
app.
So you want to create a new job find.
It doesn't matter what you put in the inside the file.
Just go ahead and name it as emoji and you want to add this feature to your chat application so that
your chat app can use emojis and then try to use that rebase operation in order marriage.
Your featured your file to your master branch.
So give this challenge Ekko and good luck.
So now let's go ahead and push all of these changes to the central repository
and here this is my web browser My central repository.
Good hop.
And if you go ahead and make sure that you are locked in first.
So if you click on your profile you should see your repositories option.
If you click on it.
So now here it is our repositories.
You can also enter this you aren't have that com slash your username in order to see the repositories.
So here we have the hello dashboard.
If you click on it here it is for example our repository here if you want to you can go ahead and create
a new repository here.
So the most important point that I want you to know about is that here it is our repository.
Hello world.
Right so this means that everybody in the good hop community has access to this project they can go
ahead and download our project and for example if you want two other people to access this project and
in that case then it's going to cause problems because others can mess up with our project or our repository
and they can push for example buggy codes or whatever to our project.
So we don't want that to happen.
We want to create access rights here so here you can see that we have this clone or download option.
If I click on it here we have a new option it says use s s h.
If you click on this one.
Now here it is used as s s h key and passphrase from account.
So let's go ahead and copy this link.
I'm going to click on this icon in order to copy it.
Now let's go ahead and open our bash application.
So because of the access rights thing that I told you about.
First we need to generate an S S H key.
So just type in here s s h dash key gen S-sh dash kitchen and then person on your keyboard.
So now it says generating Puplick slash private or as a key pair unterrified in which to save the key.
So here it is the address of the file that it is going to save the key.
C users.
The name of your user name of the computer that S-sh slash ID on the line or state.
So I'm going to press on until he again on my keyboard.
Now it says create a directory.
So here it is the directory in order to find the S-sh key fine and then it says Enter passphrase and
it is empty for no passphrase.
So if you want to specify a passphrase you can enter it here.
So I'm going to enter it here and then as you can see as I'm writing my passphrase here it is not as
showing me here letters or even little circles so it is more secure.
So don't worry if you are not seeing what is happening here you just need to enter the passphrase and
unprecedented on your keyboard.
So now it says your identification has been saved in this file in this address and your public key has
been saved in this address.
The key fingerprint is this one so hopefully that makes sense.
And this means that RSS has key is now generated and now we can go ahead and use it.
And also if you want to see the content of your SSN key file then you can just go ahead and type in
here.
The cats comment and then just paste this address here.
If it's me I need to type it here again.
So the Control-C doesn't fall here I'm going to right click on it and then click on copy.
So Chad and I see the here paste.
So then press on until you are on your keyboard.
So now here it is the S-sh keep my public S-sh key so hopefully that makes sense.
So now that we are we have this S-sh key so make sure that you are using these thought pop the public
key that we need to use on here.
Now that we have this key we need to go ahead and added to our GitHub.
So let's go ahead and first copy it is key.
I'm going to select it and then click on copy and then go back to get up and here click on your profile
and then click on settings.
Next go ahead and click on S S H and Peachi keys.
First of in if you click on new S-sh key and then we need to provide a title and then we need to paste
the excesses there.
So let's wait a little bit here.
So the title is going to be for example I'm going to say hello world.
S-sh Kee and then I'm going to paste the key here.
So now I'm going to click on at S-sh key.
So now it is asking me to enter the password of my account in good hub so that we can continue to just
enter the password and then click and confirm passport.
So here it is R S S H key.
To get hub.
This is the list of essences keys associated with your account.
If you want to you can remove them.
So now let's go ahead and open our bag.
So here it is here.
Actually it is a little bit crowded just typing here clear.
So now that we have put the S-sh key in the getup now we need to authenticate.
So just typing here.
S s h space dash capital-T space gets at sign gets hard that's come.
OK.
And then press on until key on your keyboard.
So let's wait a little bit here.
Now it says the authenticity of hostes can be established.
Arest a key fingerprint is this one.
So are you sure you want to continue connecting.
So we trust gets Hopp here.
So I'm going to just step in here.
Yes so it says yes or no.
I'm going to enter the yes and then press on into the key on my keyboard.
It has permanently added Get hup to the list of known hosts and it has entered a passphrase for this
key.
So remember that the passphrase that if we needed to specify for our S-sh keep and we could also specify
an empty string value an empty value for the password.
So if you specify a value for the passport you need to type it here.
The passphrase actually.
So I'm going to type in here.
My passport.
So you might not see the passport here.
Don't for it just intellect and unprecedented here on your keyboard we have a new message here it says
Hi this is my username you've successfully authenticated but kit but get hub does not provide shell
access.
Don't worry about this one.
Now that we are successfully authenticated we can go ahead and push our changes to get hub.
So remember always use S-sh key in order to secure your repository in getopt because we don't want anyone
else to mess up with our repository.
So now if you go to the up here you can see we have this blackout here in the S-sh keys.
If I go ahead and refresh this page let's see what happens.
Now this key is in green color.
This means that we are successfully authenticated.
So now here let me tell you that we can also have a new branch in our central repository so that we
not actually interrupt or interfere with our main branch in the get up and we can have a new branch
for our own and maybe we can name it as new features or whatever.
Or if you are actually in a team of developers then you can have your own branch there and everyone
will know that this is your for example your branch and you are working on your branch and you have
not decided to merge your branch to the master branch yet.
So you can have that here too.
So let's go ahead and let's see how it works.
First of all not now that we are in the sitting space here you can see that we have this option.
It says repositories if you click on it we can see our repository here.
Hello.
If I click on it here.
Now we are guided to this page.
And now here we have something called branch and currently it is master.
If you click on it we can see that here you can create a new branch if you enter the name of your branch.
You can just go ahead and create it.
But let's go ahead and create our branch in the command line application because it is much more professional.
And it is much more better.
So let's go ahead and open our bash or our terminal application.
So here first let's go ahead and clear this area.
So because we want to have a new branch inside a central repository here inside dispatch application
let's go ahead and so each to their first branch so I'm going to type in here get checked out and then
the name of the branch.
So if the and in here I'm going to notice that instead Apprentice's it's true you should say the name
of your branch.
So next step in here is push space origin space.
Now before we used mass there right now we're going to just refer to the name of our branch which is
going to be iffy and then press on Enter key on your keyboard in order to execute this command.
So here it says origin.
So it says the origin does not exist.
I have a typo here.
So I'm going to enter my command again.
Get push
and origin if the now let's wait a little bit here so here it says enumerating objects 14.
And it says Don.
So here you can see that it says Create a pull request for if be an get.
By visiting this you Ardell.
So now you can notice that we have a new branch inside our central repository.
So if you go ahead and you go to your central repository here it says your recently pushed branches
here we have the B.
If I click on this if the.
Now here it is our FP branch.
So here it is branch if B.
Right.
We are not inside the master branch anymore.
We have two branches the first one is the master and we have also the piece of your code inside the
first branch.
So inside the first branch we have all of these files.
We have the box.
Kickboxer Laia immobile read me all of these files and if I switch to the master branch you can see
that we only have the music of job fine and they read me that in the file.
So now hopefully you get the idea.
Now we can go ahead and so is today.
M. branch.
So here let's first clear this area and I'm going to type in here.
Good.
Check out master.
And then just step in here gets push space origin Masterson make sure that inside Apprentice's it says
Master that this means that we are currently inside the master branch.
And then I just need to push my changes to that master branch in a central repository.
So I'm going to press on and three key on my keyboard.
The process is finished.
If you go back to your central repository and here the branch is master.
So here make sure that branch is master and make sure to first refresh this page and then you can see
these changes.
You can see that all of your files are added to the master branch and you can also switch to the first
branch or your F B and you can see these files here.
So hopefully that makes sense.
So the final important point that you want to talk about here is about going back to the previous change.
So let's go ahead and open our folder and write test kits and for example go ahead and open the mobile
that Java find here.
I want to add another change I want to add another line of code to my main effort and paste it here.
And this time I want to say or let's say everyone.
So let's save this file and then close our project.
And then let's end there because I want to see the contents of my mobile that fight.
So Chatz Mauboy thought Java.
So here you can see the content.
And here you can see this line of code everyone.
So for example I don't like this new change that I added to my mobile that are fine and I want to go
back to the previous version of this file.
So now that we have changed our file you know that first we need to commit our changes and then we can
decide whether we liked our change or not.
Or in that case we can decide that we want to go back to the previous version or previous snapshot because
what I told you about snapshot or comments is that we have the updated or in other words we have a snapshot
that contains the most updated code.
So now we don't have that snapshot and this means that we cannot go back to the previous comment.
So first we need to create a comment I'm going to say get it because we have only modified our file.
We can say dash a space dash em and then two coats.
And then I can say modified more by the age of a fight two coats and then press enter on your keyboard.
So next go ahead and use this command get log in order to just put the lugs inside the command line
tool.
So next you have the lugs and then you need to find the specific log that is related to the previous
changes of your file.
So for example in this case our file is more than that of a file.
So I want to roll back to the previous changes so you need to take a look at the logs and see version
of the file you want to roll back to.
So here for example you have the date.
So for example I want to go back to these two the changes that I made at this hour.
Right.
So you just need to find that specific date and find that specific commit here you can see the commit
and then you can go ahead and copy the first 8 digits of this hexadecimal code.
So one two three four five six seven eight capitis the first eight hex decimal digits and then go back
to the bash file or the Terminal application.
So here you just need to enter get.
So make sure that you are inside this and retested directory.
I am inside the master branch.
So get check out space and then you need to paste the hexadecimal code here.
Space.
And then the name of the file.
So it is more byde that Joe and then present it on your keyboard.
Now let's go ahead and let's see what is the content of our mobile device are cats more ways that Java.
So here you can see now we are rolled back to this version of the file.
We don't have that specific line of code that we had at here.
We added here because we wanted to go back to the previous comment.
Now here you can see this line of code.
This means that you are rolled back to the previous version of this file and everything is working perfectly.
But remember these changes can only be rolled back if you commit your changes.
OK.
We have snapshots of our project.
So for example you create a snapshot and later you know that's all you'll find out that that specific
change is not working and you want to roll back to the commit period to the previous comment.
So you just go ahead and use this come and get checked out.
And then at their first digits of the hexadecimal code of the commits that you want to roll back to
and then the name of the fight more by that.
In this case and then everything will be working fine.
So make sure to use this cat's command in order to always check your content of your file and see that
everything is working perfectly.
So let's see what we have learned so far in this video.
We have learned about Padel and development but overall we have learned about the working space.
The project that you're working on and then we add our changes to the staging area the index get index
and then we have the local repository.
So for example because it's our changes.
So that's why we need the local repository so that we have these snapshots of our project and then we
have the remote repository that is actually our central repository.
In this case it is getup and we use the push pull operations in order to push our changes to our remote
repository or we use the pool operation to pool our tune changes back from the remote's repository.
So this is really all we have learned about parallel development about the branching concept.
We also learned about merging and rebasing.
And then finally we could actually push all of our changes to the remote repository.
So in the next year two or three of we are going to learn how to integrate the kit to Android studio.
So I look forward to seeing you in the next video.