Hello everyone.
Welcome to this video.
In this story are you going to integrate get into Android studio.
So now let's go ahead and create a new project and choose empty activity.
So let's name the project to be good.
Android studio.
So just typing here to get Android studio and then the package name the save location path make sure
that the language is Java.
You can choose Castine if you want.
Because in this project we just want to integrate the kit into Android studio so we don't want to write
Java code here or cotton coats and a minimum API level is going to be 16 API 16 and click on finish.
So now let me click on.
Yes.
And these experiments are a great great feature.
Now let's go ahead and let's see.
Let's actually test the gate so that we can be sure that they get is actually installed on our computer.
So if you don't have that get installed on your computer you need to go ahead and download and install
it.
And when you actually Dan Lothian raid the studio they get also comes with Andrew the studio and you
already have that get on your computer.
But it's better to test.
So let's go ahead and click on file.
If you are using Mac just click on Android to suit your preferences.
And here click on settings next.
Go ahead and click on version control here.
Open it and then choose.
Get up.
Just click on it.
Now here it does not get Harbach counts added.
So we need to first add an archetype account to Android studio.
So just click on an account here.
So the server is get hot that's come.
Now you need to enter our username and password here.
And when you enter your credentials click on luggin And if you don't have a good account you need to
go ahead and create one.
So just click on and log in.
Now we should wait here so here you can see my account is added to Android studio here.
So now that we have added our account to Android studio here below is version control.
If you open it you can see these kids.
If you click on it here it is the path to today kids start a fire inside my computer and if you click
on the test button here it's gonna show you a success message and it's going to give you the version
of the key.
It's sort of I just need to click on OK.
So now I am sure that the kit is installed on my computer.
Let's go ahead and click on apply or.
OK so now everything is fine.
So now in order to share our project and get up at the top and you have this option VC it's just going
to click on it.
And then here you can see some options.
For example we have the local history enable version control integration wiseass operations pop up and
some other options.
Let's go ahead and go into the import into Version control and then we have this option that says share
project and get up let's click on it and let's wait a little bit here.
So here it's going to create a repository for us and get up.
So it is giving us this repository name as a suggestion.
You can if you want you can change it.
Get Android studio.
So this is the name of our project so you can also check the search box if you want your product to
be private.
We have the remote here the remote name and the description.
So about 30 modes and the description for now let's just click on share.
So here we have something really interesting.
We have this window that says at Feis for initial coming so we don't have to write code here command
line codes here we just need to interact with this application and just click on OK and then come it
will be executed.
So here not is that it is actually committing all of these files here.
So because this our initial commit of this project I suggest that you do actually commit all of these
files to a central repository because of this in our central repository we don't have these files.
So first make sure that you put all of these files into the get hub and then event later when you for
example change a specific file.
For example you may only change main activity class so in that case you only want to commit to the main
activity class.
You don't have to for example commits the grateful codes.
Or maybe the MIF map folder or the driver folder.
So here make sure that all of these checkboxes are checked.
And later when you don't want it for example a specific file to be committed you just need to uncheck
that checkbox of a specific folder or a file.
And here we have the commit message remember.
So I'm gonna say get Android studio first come.
OK.
Now let's go ahead and click on.
Now it's pushing to get harbormaster.
This is going to be our master branch here at the bottom.
And if you click on it you can see that background tasks that is being executed.
So here we have this message that says successfully shared project and get up.
And here we have this link to get Android to you.
I'm going to click on it.
So here it is our remote repository and get up.
This is the name of our repository kids Android studio.
And then here these are our Android studio files.
You can see here all the cradle files.
So inside the app folder for example if you click on it you can see it is fine.
RC The source may.
And then here you can see the job folder.
If I click on it here it is our main main activity that job.
And here you can see all the codes here.
So everything is working perfectly.
So the branch is the master.
Right.
And let's go ahead and just click on Android studio.
So this is our project in.
Get up and we could successfully by just adding our accounts to an android studio and then using the
vicissitude we could commit our project here and here it is a snapshot of our project on get up.
So now if you go back to Andrew Estadio you can see that at the top menu here in say the spot below
the start menu.
We have some new icons.
We have this good section.
And the first icon here is to update the project.
And the second icon is to commit to our changes.
So if we go ahead and click on it now it's going on.
Give me the files that are not actually committed in the previous comment or maybe the modified files.
So for example if I go ahead.
So here when I wanted to close that window it is advised to get.
Do you want to add the following file to get.
So here this file this vitiates that examen file is added recently.
So here we can actually go ahead and at this five this vicious that there is a fight to get up.
So I just need to click on.
Yes.
And now let's say this main activity class let's add a new line of code here inside is uncreate method.
So I'm going to say lock that so first we need to specify the TAC comma and then I'm going inside the
code to step in here message semicolon.
Now if we modify our main activity class now here inside this section I'm going to Caly can come in
it does come into icon and here it says that the main activity class here is changed.
We can't come in.
So here we can see this lock statement that we added to the uncreate Meffert of their main activity
class and here inside this section you can see all the files that should be committed.
The main activity class should be committed.
So it is one added one might one modify it.
So now we can go ahead and commit our changes.
So that is that when it says one that it is related to these vitiates that exemplified that we added
to their staging area so we can go ahead and click on commit so here it says please specify come with
message.
So that's why I told you that you must specify a message for your Kemet.
So I'm going to say main activity and Vizier's
exemplified.
So for example this is my message.
You can name it whatever you want.
And here I just need to click on Kermit.
So now it has two files committed main activity Rizzi as exemplified committed.
So Claymates means that now we have our new snapshot of this project of this gets Android studio project.
Now we can go ahead and push this snapshot this commit to the central repository or to the remote repository.
This update projects I'm going to click on it and here we have some options we have for example using
marriage rebase here it is branch the fall.
So we're going to use that Master branch here.
We have the stash and Shell.
So stash is actually for example we have some unfinished changes in our project and we want to save
it.
And then for example applied later.
So stash helps us to use this feature to apply our unfinished changes later.
So just check this check box don't worry about this one here.
The branch is going to be difficult.
And I just want to go ahead and click on OK.
So now it says that all files are up to date.
So in order to push our project to the central repository we need to go ahead and click on the commit
again here.
So it says no changes detected.
Right.
So I'm going to change something here so I'm just going to copy this line of code and paste it here
again and then I'm going to go ahead and click on it.
So because we have a new change here I am going to come with my changes here.
But if you hover over this button and click on this dropdown we have two other options.
We have come out and push we have create patch.
So if you go ahead and click on come it and push let's see what happens.
So now it's going to add to the project to that master branch.
So now we have two committees.
This is the previous commit and we had the busiest that exemplified remember.
And this is our latest committee.
So here in this committee we added a second a lock statement.
OK.
So now I'm going to select both of these commits and into skilly can push and you can see that it says
push successful push to come it's to region master to the master branch.
So now if you go ahead so here if you go ahead and open that remote repository get Andrew in studio.
Let's go ahead and just refresh this page here.
I'm going to go ahead and open the app folder and sarcy main and then up let's get it back go back to
main and then click on this Java package and main activity that Java.
So here you should see the two lines of code that are added here.
And also if you go ahead and click on come it's here.
So if I click on get Andrew Android studio here we have free comets right.
If you go ahead and click on Kermit's you can see all of these comments here.
So here it this is our first comment.
We have our second Cometh and we have this one.
So our first coming out is actually for 20 minutes ago.
Second time it's 12 minutes ago and our latest commit is in three minutes ago.
So in our second comment here we only had one line of code one LUGG statement.
And if I click on back and here it is our latest coming out here we can see that we have to look statements.
So when I say come it I mean different snapshots of the project.
So hopefully that makes sense and make sure that you always always use come in all of your projects.
It doesn't matter if it is whether it is a practice project or a test project or your complex project.
You should always use Get up get and get up and always come into your changes and create snapshots out
of your project because you are going to just make the process of the debarking very easy.
And we have another way to push our changes to the good repository So for example if I go ahead and
copy this line of code here and paste it here so I'm going to change it to my message and here at the
top menu.
Just go ahead and click on vicis and then he'll go to get.
So here we have all of these operations.
So we have come to find and we have the reverse option.
We have branches.
And here we have marriage changes.
So here you can see the clone option.
We have fetch pool and push.
These are the two most important operations that you should know about.
And we also have the rebase option and the Create pool request so you can see all of these operations
here.
But you just literally can't visit as kids and you can have all of these options here.
That's really cool about this fetch here.
This is just a part of the pool operation.
So when you use the pool operation you get the data and then merge it on your for example your master
or branch but Fich just gets the data from the server from the central repository.
So don't worry about this fetch here.
We just need to work on the push and the pool.
So now let's go ahead and click on push and here it's going to add to changes to our Master branch.
So here it is no come selector.
So first we need to commit our changes remember.
So here this green icon here and see if I click on it here it says that we have a new commit.
We have a new code.
It is actually highlighting it in a green color.
So here let's actually change this message and say that my first message.
And then just go ahead and you can't.
You can just click on commit and then push it later.
Or you can come commit and push.
So I'm going to ask if he can commit and then I need to go ahead and can he can Vizier's kids and then
push.
So now we have this my first message coming here.
This is the snapshot of the project of the fight that is actually changed.
And I just need to click on push now.
It says that the push is successful.
So if you want to you can also go ahead and use the pool operation.
So.
Yes.
And go to get and then click on pool.
Now it says here it is that gets route.
So this is the address of my project in my computer.
Here it is the address of the remote repository.
And then it's here it is Raymie the branches to merge that Master branch.
And here we have the strategy so don't forget about this one here.
You just literally can pool and then it's going to pull the project from the remote repository and it's
going to be injected automatically into my project kit and really stood you to this path.
So you don't have to worry about anything here and here it says pool operation.
So because we have no items here because we haven't changed anything it is already updated.
We can also go ahead and play around with these other options for example branches here.
You can create a new branch if you want.
We have local branches we have remote branches.
You already know what to do about these branches.
So you just need to go ahead and work on these options and just play around with it a little bit.
And because you are you are going to use it in all of your projects from now on.
OK.
So this is the end of this section of the course.
You have learned everything you needed to know about get and get help.
Now it's your turn.
And again make sure to use good in each and every project that you create.
Really your programming projects.
So thank you very much for watching.
I'll see you next.